[Music]
in this video you will learn the
mountain pose also known as tadasana
start by standing erect with your feet
together and your arms relaxed alongside
your
body distribute your weight evenly
across the soles of both your feet and
press your toes down against the floor
inhale deeply and raise your arms and
interlock your fingers with your palms
out to reach towards the
ceiling get onto the tips of your toes
with your heels
together tighten your knees pull up your
ham string and contract your
hips pull in your abdomen and expand
your chest as you fill up your lungs and
hold your breath for a moment as you
continue to
stretch look at a point straight in
front of
you relax and breathe out as you once
again bring your arms beside your
thighs you can also try the pose with
your feet slightly
apart this pose improves your posture
firms your abdomen and buttock and
strengthens your feet legs and hips you
have now learned the dasana the mountain
pose
[Music]